<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smart Water Filter | DVA NGUYEN</title><link>https://example.com/tag/smart-water-filter/</link><atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/smart-water-filter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Smart Water Filter</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Smart Water Filter</title><link>https://example.com/tag/smart-water-filter/</link></image><item><title>Mini smart water treatment station for motorhomes (EZA Water)</title><link>https://example.com/project/smartwaterfilter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/project/smartwaterfilter/</guid><description>&lt;p>LAVI is a start-up company operating in the field of accessories for Motorhomes. In collaboration with SOPLAIR company, LAVI seeks to develop a range of intelligent products to improve the comfort of the motorhome: the EZA range.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The mission of EZA Water was to reprocess used water, there by, improve the comfort and autonomy of motorhome owners. The entrusted mission was to design an intelligent and low-consumption electronic system to check the operation of the hydraulic system using sensors (i.e., detecting the clogging and leaking problems). This system can communicate with the user via a touch screen and a beep sound. The maintenance software makes it possible to modify the parameters of the system and to recover the recorded data files with a micro SD card. Thus, the company has a simple and effective tool to analyze the causes of malfunction and ensure product traceability.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Mr. Nguyen and his team (as 4 future engineers of Grenoble INP-ESISAR) researched and developed (full-time) this product for LAVI company during six months (Jan - Jul, 2017). The main tasks of Mr. Nguyen focus on the design of a Printed Circuit Boards (PCB), Human Machine Interface (HMI) development, and sensors/signal processing.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>