<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts | DVA NGUYEN</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/</link><atom:link href="https://example.com/coauthors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Posts</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Posts</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/</link></image><item><title>Brahim TAMADAZTE</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/brahim_tamadazte/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/brahim_tamadazte/</guid><description>&lt;p>Brahim Tamadazte holds a Ph.D. in Robotics from the “Univ. of Franche-Comté” in 2009 and a Habilitation (HdR) in 2019.
Previously, he obtained a MS degree in Robotics and Intelligent Systems from the “Univ. of Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris VI)” in 2005.
He has also trained as an Engineer in Control Theory at the “Univ. Mouloud Mammeri de Tizi-Ouzou”, Algeria.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He works in different fields of medical microrobotics such as image-guided surgery, mechatronics design, medical imaging, and compressed sensing.
From 2012 to 2020, he was a member of the FEMTO-ST Institute (AS2M Dep.) as CNRS Senior researcher.
Since 2020, he has joined the ISIR lab located in the facilities of Sorbonne University (Jussieu).
His work is part of the activities of the AGATHE team (CNRS, Inserm ERL U1150, SU).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cédric GIRERD</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/cedric_girerd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/cedric_girerd/</guid><description>&lt;p>Cédric Girerd received a PhD in Medical Robotics (2018) from the University of Strasbourg, France,
in collaboration with the ICube-AVR Laboratory in Strasbourg and the FEMTO-ST Institute in Besançon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He worked at the FEMTO-ST Institute, Univ. Bourgogne Franche-Comté, CNRS (2018-2019) and at Morimoto Lab, University of California San Diego (2019-2022) as a Postdoctoral Researcher in Medical Robotics.
He is currently CNRS Researcher, LIRMM, Montpellier, France. His research interests include the design and control of continuum and soft robots for minimally-invasive surgery.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ionela PRODAN</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/ionela_prodan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/ionela_prodan/</guid><description>&lt;p>She received the B.E. degree from the University &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Politehnica&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; of Bucharest, Romania (2009) and the PhD in Control Engineering at Supélec, Gif-sur-Yvette, France (2012).
For one and a half year she was a postdoctoral researcher within the Chair on Systems Science and the Energetic Challenge - EDF, École Centrale Paris and Supélec, France (2013 - 2014).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She is currently an Associated Professor (HdR) at Grenoble INP - ESISAR and LCIS (Laboratoire de Conception et d&amp;rsquo;Intégration des Systèmes) laboratory, France.
Her research interests include: automatic control and optimization solver applied to multiple autonomous vehicles and energy systems. &lt;br>
resilience in interconnected infrastructure systems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Jérôme SZEWCZYK</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/jerome_szewczyk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/jerome_szewczyk/</guid><description>&lt;p>Jérôme Szewczyk received a MS degree (1994)
in mechanical engineering from University of
Compiegne, FR and a PhD degree (1998) in robotics at University of Paris VI.
He was assistant professor from 2000 to 2010 at University of Versailles and
is now full professor at Sorbonne University at the
Institut des Systemes Intelligents et de Robotique.
He is the author of over 100 technical publications.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>His research activities concern the design of
sensors and actuators for meso-robotics based on
smart materials and the optimal design of robotic
structures for surgical applications. In particular, he is interested in the
development and optimization of robotic surgical instruments and active
flexible catheters for minimally invasive interventions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Kanty RABENOROSOA</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/kanty_rabenorosoa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/kanty_rabenorosoa/</guid><description>&lt;p>Kanty Rabenorosoa holds the M.S. degree (2007)
in electrical engineering from INSA Strasbourg, FR
and the Ph.D. in automatic control (2010) from Univ.
de Franche-Comté, FR. He was a postdoc fellow at
LIRMM (2011/2012) within ARAKNESS european project.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He is currently Professor at FEMTO-ST
Institute in AS2M department. His research interests
are continuum and soft robots at small scales for
medical applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Laurent LEFEVRE</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/laurent_lefevre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/laurent_lefevre/</guid><description>&lt;p>Laurent Lefèvre got his BSc from the Ecole Polytechnique de Bruxelles (1991) and his MSc in applied mathematics from Ecole Polytechnique de Louvain (1994), both in Belgium.
Then he moved to France and got his PhD in control from Ecole Centrale de Lille (Cristal lab, 1999).
In 2000, he obtained an associated professor position in the Grenoble control lab (Gipsa lab) and from 2005 in the Lyon lab for process and control (LAGEP).
Since 2011 he is full professor with the Laboratoire de Conception et d’Intégration des Systèmes (LCIS) and Grenoble Institute of Technology (Grenoble INP) in the fields of applied mathematics and control.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>His current domains of interest are numerical methods for control, structured modelling for complex systems and nonlinear control. Laurent Lefèvre was involved in various collaborative research projects related to complex water systems, complex thermodynamics systems, smart DC microgrids and plasma physics.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Laurent TAVERNIER</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/laurent_tarvernier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/laurent_tarvernier/</guid><description>&lt;p>Laurent Tavernier is a professor at Univ. Hospital of Besançon, Univ. Bourgogne Franche-Comté (France) and is Head of Ear-Nose-Throat (ENT) Service of the Besançon University Hospital.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He is also the coordinator of the µRoCS project.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Olivier GAIFFE</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/olivier_gaiffe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/olivier_gaiffe/</guid><description>&lt;p>Olivier Gaiffe obtained his Ph.D. degree in Engineering Science from the University of Franche-Comté,
Besançon, France in 2009. He is now working at Univ. Hospital of Besançon as a research engineer. His current research interests include fluorescence, optical sensing and instrumentation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Olivier LEHMANN</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/olivier_lehmann/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/olivier_lehmann/</guid><description>&lt;p>Olivier Lehmann received the Engineer degree (M.S. degree) in automation, mechanics and computer sciences from ENSMM, Besançon, France, in
2000. He was an engineer in charge of technology transfer at the Institut de Productique and then at the Institut Pierre Vernier. In this context, he developed
numerous robotics solutions dedicated to SMEs for 13 years and helped SMEs in their development.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He is currently research engineer at FEMTO-ST. He is in charge of the development of several micronanorobotic stations in vacuum or non-vacuum environment.
His scientific fields are robotics, control, vision and the development of integrated solutions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Patrick ROUGEOT</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/patrick_rougeot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/patrick_rougeot/</guid><description>&lt;p>Patrick Rougeot received the engineer degree
in mechanics and microtechniques from ENSMM
(Ecole Nationale Supérieure de Mécanique et des
Microtechniques), Besançon, FR (1990).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He is currently a senior research engineer at
FEMTO-ST Institute within the AS2M department.
He developed a high expertise in microrobotics and
related fields for both industrial and medical purposes. He works in micromechatronics design and
microrobot control for minimally-invasive surgery
applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Yann NGUYEN</title><link>https://example.com/coauthors/yann_nguyen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/coauthors/yann_nguyen/</guid><description>&lt;p>Yann Nguyen is an ENT professor at the Otolaryngology Department, in Hospital Pitié Salpêtrière (Sorbonne University, AP-HP), in Paris, France.
His clinical activities are focused on middle ear surgery, cochlear implantation and lateral skull base surgery.
He obtained the PhD degree on “robot based surgery for cochlear implantation” at Sorbonne University (2011).
He keeps working on robotics in the &amp;ldquo;Hearing Institute&amp;rdquo; (Institut Pasteur/Inserm). The goal is to design and evaluate surgical solutions from lab bench to operating room for hearing loss.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He won the Scientific Emergence Prize in 2018 for clinical research. The prize honored his contributions in developing the first surgical robot for cochlear implantation.
This led to the design of the RoboTol ear-surgery robot and its commercialization by the Collin Medical company in 2017.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He is a member of the µRoCS project.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>